<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Python on Be Humble</title>
    <link>http://pra-dan.github.io/tags/python/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Python on Be Humble</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://pra-dan.github.io/tags/python/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Synthetic Dataset using Blender&#43;Python: Part 2</title>
      <link>http://pra-dan.github.io/blog/blender-and-python-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pra-dan.github.io/blog/blender-and-python-1/</guid>
      <description>Now that we are comfortable with the Blender starters, we can start using Python to automate some of its aspects and generate a synthetic dataset.
Pre-requisites: I will be using Ubuntu 20.01 and Blender 2.91.
Objective: To generate a dataset using Blender and Python, with the characteristics:
 Assume our object is centered at the origin (0,0,0) Capture the object from a particular distance (R), in a circular path, a total of 10 images The script should also output camera locations and orientation (in Z axis) along with the frames  Such dataset may help us find out the camera/robot&amp;rsquo;s location given a test image; not so simple as it sounds ;)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Synthetic Dataset using Blender&#43;Python: Part 1</title>
      <link>http://pra-dan.github.io/blog/blender-and-python-0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pra-dan.github.io/blog/blender-and-python-0/</guid>
      <description>The tutorial explores basic functionalities of Blender that are required for our goal: generating synthetic dataset using Blender+Python. Blender can do pretty much anything related to graphic manipulation, from Sculpting to VFX, Blender has you covered.
Pre-Requisite: Install Blender from official site. I am using 2.91.0. on Ubuntu 20.01.
$ sudo snap install blender --classic #installs current stable version Now, Launch it by clicking on the icon or using your terminal and hitting blender + Enter (Highly Recommended).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>